我真不敢相信都市新闻一台\n现在还转发给你这些粉丝的来信
I can't believe Metro News One is just\nforwarding you all this fan mail now.
是啊 我大概4个月前辞职的
I know. I quit like four months ago.
哇 你的粉丝比我想象的要多
Wow, you had more fans than I thought.
并且只有60%来自监狱的囚犯哦
And only about 60% of\nthem are prison inmates.
他们都怎么想的?
What are these guythinking?
我已经度过"约会囚徒"的阶段了
I am way past my\n"dating prisoners" phase.
就像是 嗨 我已不再是19岁了
It's like, hello, I'm not 19 anymore.
呃 Lottery Girl开始了\n(抽奖节目)
Uh, uh, Lottery Girl's on.
我对这些女人感到遗憾
I just feel sorry for these women.
这就是为什么电视节目每况愈下
This is where broadcast\ncareers go to die.
看看 我来弄点乐子\n我研究了新的娱乐方式
Check it out. I make it fun.\nI invented a little game.
今晚的幸运数字是...
Tonight's Lotto numbers are...
19...\nnineteen...
你来到纽约在美食街被一个星探\n"发现"的年龄
Age you moved to New York after a\nphotographer "discovered" you at a food court
他说他能让你上"世界时尚"杂志
and said he'd get you in Vogue magazine.
53...\nfifty-three...
在你发现被骗前已\n为所谓"时尚"杂志拍下的半裸照片的数量
Number of semi-nude pictures he took you before\nyou realized he had no connection to Vogue magazine.
22...\ntwenty-two...
你对外声称自己的年龄
Age you claim you are.
31...\nthirty-one...
你实际的年龄
Age you actually are.
45...\nforty-five...
这是我把你拽进出租车 脱掉你的衣服\n带到我的浴缸里所需的分钟数
Number of minutes it would take me to get you\ninto a cab, out of your dress, and into my Jacuzzi.
今晚的大奖数字是...
And tonight's Super Big Ball is...
我们从浴缸出来后发生的\n(指的是大奖)
What happens after\nweet out of the Jacuzzi.
如何啊?
What up?
老爸老妈浪漫史\n第四季 第14集
How I Met Your\nMother Season04 Episode14
孩子们 2009年的冬天来了\nRobin已经失业几个月了
Kids, by the winter of 2009, Robin\nhad been unemployed for months.
但仍有一丝希望
But there was a glimmer of hope.
试镜怎么样?
How'd the audition go?
我进去时感觉很好
Well, I went in there\nfeeling really good.
听说只有两个竞争者
I heard it was just me up\nagainst two other girls.
我们在听呢
Listening.
我是Robin Scherbatsky
Robin Scherbatsky.
你呢?
And you are?
很明显你从没在丹佛待过
You've obviously never\nspent any time in Denver.
Rochelle Harper 新闻中心12台
Rochelle Harper, News Center 12.
我们是洛杉矶唯一在连续5年内\n位居第一的电视台
We were only the number-one station\nin the Rockies for five straight years.
我曾是这里都市新闻台的主持人
I was an anchor here in\ntown at Metro News One.
哦 主持人
Ooh, an anchor.
你肯定有杀手锏吧
You must have a killer signoff phrase.
什么?
I'm sorry?
你要有个绝活
You gotta have a killer signoff phrase.
像Walter Cronkite "事情就是这样"
Like Walter Cronkite:\n"And that's the way it is."
那么你的是?
So what's yours?
我只是简单说句 感谢收看都市新闻频道\n祝您晚安
Well, I would just always end with a simple From all\nof us here at Metro News One, have a good evening.
我的是 "所有在Barney家里的人 出去"
Mine is: "From all of us here\nat Barney's apartment, get out."
你没让这些家伙打败你 是吧?
You didn't let those reporter\nbitches psych you out, did you?
总统的经济咨询小组希望\n在月底递交给国会前
and the President's economic team is\nhoping to have a proposal before Congress
得到提案
by the end of the month.
感谢收看新闻10频道 祝您晚安
From all of us here at News\nTen, have a good evening.
晚安 纽约
So, good night, New York.
愿梦想和未来点亮前方的路
And may the road ahead be\nlit with dreams and tomorrows.
未来也被梦想点亮... 同样的
Which are lit with dreams... also.
那太糟了
That's terrible.
很不好... 同样的
And bad... also.
我还没说完
I wasn't done.
挺起身来 纽约
Stand tall, New York.
诚信 环保
Trustworthy. Recycling.
带避孕套
Wear a condom.
带避孕套?
Wear a condom?
我不会成为10频道的主持人的 对么?
I'm not gonna be the new\nChannel Ten anchor, am I?
有个声音说 不会
This just in. No.
也许是你简历的问题
Maybe the problem is your r\sum\.
看我的多清晰明了?
See how mine is lean and mean?
你的太乱了
Yours is too cluttered.
难道你的简历上的信息都是有用的?
Oh, like everything on\nyour r\sum\ is so relevant?
"节目主播 88.1兆赫 Wesleyan大学广播台?"
"Program Director,88. 1\nWesleyan University Radio?"
哦 天
Oh, God.
X博士?你还在自吹自擂这个?
Dr. X? You're still\nbragging about Dr. X?
谁是X博士?
Who was Dr. X?
没有人知道
Nobody knows.
- 他是神秘的天才D.J\n- 是Ted
- He was this genius mystery D.J.\n- It was Ted.
他的身份直到今天仍是个迷
His identity remains\na secret to this day.
是Ted
It was Ted.
但是这个电波中的幽灵\n使大学广播焕然一新
But this phantom of the airwaves\nchanged the very face of college radio.
- 是Ted\n- 而且你的节目很傻
- It was Ted.\n- And your show sucked.
X博士在此 在隐蔽的角落里来告诉你真相
Dr. X here, shooting truth bullets\nat you from an undisclosed location.
因为若被人发现 我将被封口
Because if they knew where\nI was, they'd shut me down.
你在学生活动中心三楼游戏室旁边的屋里 你这笨蛋
You're on the third floor of the Student\nCenter next to the game room, you tool.
我收到了很多给我意见的来信\n关于学校的饮食计划有种族歧视的含义
I've been getting a lot of letters about\nmyegment on how racist the school's meal plan is.
没人知道你在哪怎么给你寄信 傻子?
How are you getting letters if no\none knows where you are, douche?
这就是为什么我预备周一的半夜\n在食堂外面组织抗议的原因
That's why I'm organizing a happening\noutside the dining hall, Monday at midnight.
是时候该教训这些后勤傀儡头子们的玩忽职守了
It's high time the Food Service puppet masters\ntook ignorance and injustice off the menu.
Ted 我们四号位缺人
Hey, Ted, we need a fourth for foosball.
另外 你在这干吗呢?
What are you doing in here, anyway?
伙计 先出去! 我马上就来
Dude, get out of here!\nI'll be there in a second.
记着 食堂 周一 半夜见
So remember,dining\nhall, Monday, midnight.
又一个X博士事件发生了
Another Dr. X happening.
我会在那儿 因为X标志着现-现-现-现场...
I'll be there, because X\nmarks the spot-ot-ot-ot-ot...
如果你认为别人会稀罕你的节目\n他们不-不-不-不会...
If you think people liked your\nshow, they did not-ot-ot-ot...
这个好奇怪 看你的粉丝来信中有这个
This is weird. Look what got\nmixed in with your fan mail.
什么?
What?
来自美国移民局的
It's from the U.S.Department\nof Immigration.
邮戳是两个月前
It's postmarked two months ago.
不是吧
Oh, boy.
是什么?
What iit?
是说我的工作签证
It's about my work visa.
除非我找到工作在接下来的...
Unless I can find a job in the next...
七天内 否则我将被遣送回加拿大
seven days, they're gonna\nsend me back to Canada.
我不相信你可能会被赶出美国
u might be kicked out of the country.
我知道 我的生活都在这
I know. My whole life is here.
不 我们不能让它发生
No. We won't let this happen.
我们会帮你找个工作
I mean, one of us will\nhelp you find a job.
是的 我猜我会在学校给你找点事干
Yeah, I bet I can get you\nsomething at my school.
不 大家... 那样行不通的
No, guys... It doesn't work that way.
Robin只有从事她自己专业的工作\n才能得到工作签证
Robin only gets her work visa\nif she gets a job in her field.
我猜如果你嫁给个美国人的话就会留下
I mean, you know what, I guess you\ncould stay if you married a U.S.citizen.
是的 那样可以
Yeah, that could work.
哦 不 不 他们不会按程序处理\n并及时得到官方认可的 那样不行
Oh, no, no. They could never process that\nand make it official in time. That won't work.
我完了 我三个月来一直寄出我的带子 \n没有任何结果
I'm screwed. I've been sending out\nmy reel for three months, and nothing.
也许你带子里有些东西人们无法理解
Well, maybe there's something in your\nreel that people aren't responding to.
我们来看看 好吗?
Let's take a look at it, right?
Robin Scherbastsky
新闻记者
********
Robin Scherbastsky 现场直播\n亚大巴斯卡河
**********
问的好 Norm
That's a good question, Norm.
好 第一个是我年轻时\n曾是Red Deer 22频道的记者
Okay, the first thing is from when I was\na cub reporter for Channel 22 in Red Deer.
在艾伯塔 \n在加拿大
In Alberta. In Canada.
- 哦 对\n- 哦 加拿大
- Oh, right.\n- Oh, Canada.
雪现在下的很大
Well, the snow's\ncoming down pretty hard,
但那些勇敢的渔人仍快乐的竞争于
but these intrepid fishermen are\nstill happy to be out competing
亚大巴斯卡河的贝斯钓鱼活动中\n这是每年的8月1日的一个传统
in Lake Athabasca's Bass Fishing\nJamboree, an August 1st tradition.
该你了 Norm
Back to you, Norm.
怎么了? 那是我第一个工作
What? That was my first job.
它说明我来自哪里
It shows where I came from.
除非三秒内你被一只熊袭击了\n并且你用腿夹住它的脖子
Unless a bear attacks you in the next three\nseconds and you snap its neck with your legs,
那就和你的带子没关了
that has no business being on your reel.
不 不 我明白了 明白了
No, no, I get it, I get it.
你来自于哪里也是你介绍自己的一种方式
Where you're from is part\nof who you're selling.
比如说 在我的简历"特殊技能"那一栏
For instance, under "special\nskills" on my r\sum\,
我提到了明尼苏达州
I mention that back in Minnesota,
我是尼科奈县1995年扣篮比赛的冠军
I was the 1995 Nicollet\nCounty Slam Dunk Champion.
你把扣篮冠军写在简历里?
You put dunk champion on your r\sum\?
是啊 为什么不呢?
Yeah, why wouldn't you?
很多公司有篮球队的
A lot of companies\nhave basketball teams.
让他们知道霹雳香草\n仍能将石头扔进洞内是件好事
It's good for them to know that Vanilla\nThunder can still take the rock to the hole.
他们叫你霹雳香草?
They called you Vanilla Thunder?
是啊 霹雳香草
Yeah, Vanilla Thunder.
无名的英雄 魔术之手
The Ghost in the Post.\nThe Human Turnstile.
我当然... 没有扣过这么多篮咯
I didn't... I didn't play that much D.
你现在不能扣篮了
You can't still dunk.
当然能
Of course I can.
我意思是以前能...直到... 直到现在
Well, I mean I could...\nuntil... until recently.
直到你负伤
Until the injury.
这叫做髂腰肌腱炎
It's called iliopsoas tendonitis.
哦 天哪 听起来太糟了
Oh, Yikes. That sounds bad.
通常被称作舞者的臀部
It's more commonly\nknown as dancer's hip.
Goodman医生...
Dr. Goodman...
拜托! 髂腰肌腱炎
Oh, come on! Iliopsoas tendonitis.
这是它的叫法\n它只能这么叫
That's what it's called.\nThat's all it's called.
髂腰肌腱炎
Iliopsoas tendonitis.
这是一种篮球运动的损伤\n没什么好惊讶的
It's a basketball injury.\nYou know, it's no big whoop.
舞者的臀部 \nMarshall得了一种叫舞者臀部的病
Dancer's hip, Marshall has\nsomething called dancer's hip.
好了 不 不 别这样
Okay, no, no, okay.
他们这么叫 \n是因为芭蕾舞演员经常有这种损伤
They only call it that, look, because\nit's very common with ballet dancers.
告诉我 \n你班级内的其他女孩有舞者的臀部么?
So, tell me, do any of the other little\ngirls in your class have dancer's hip?
是 当然了
Yeah, sure.
- 我有个技术性问题\n- 什么?
- I have more of a technical question.\n- Yes?
你下面没有那东西时跳起来是不是更容易?
Is it easier to dance when you\ndon't have external genitalia?
不要说这个问题\n说点正常的
Good, don't build to\nthat-- just go right for it.
拜托 大家 \nMarshall不是因为跳舞受的这个伤
Guys, come on. Marshall didn't\nget this injury from dancing.
谢谢你 Lily
Thank you, Lily.
很明显 他上次骑马去Gyno时\n马镫有些宽了
Clearly, the stirrups were set a little\ntoo wide during his last trip to the gyno.
伙计们 在Marshall哭之前\n我不得不打断你们
Guys, I hate to cut you off\nbefore Marshall bursts into tears,
但是 Robin 看看这个\n你需要的是一个牛逼的视频简历
but, Robin, check this out. What\nyou need is an awesome video r\sum\.
像我的这个
Like mine.
我隆重呈献为 Barneysvideoresume.com\n(Barney帅呆了视频.com)
I present: Barneysvideoresume.com.
你好
Oh, hello.
Barney Stinson 你在商业方面取得了巨大成功
Barney Stinson, you've achieved\ngreat success in business,
还有体育方面 人际关系方面\n给很多人以启示
athletics and personal relationships and\nhave been an inspiration to many people.
这声音是你吗?
Is that you?
你在采访自己吗?
Are you interviewing yourself?
怎么能是我呢? \n那家伙是英国人
How can it be me? That guy's British.
你会对那些想激发自己潜能的\n仰慕者推荐些什么呢?
What would you recommend to yr numerous admirers\nwho want to reach their highest potential?
还有点苏格兰味儿
And a wee bit Scottish.
首先你要知道的是\n成功不会自己向你走来
The first thing you need to know about\nsuccess is that it doesn't just come to you.
大多数人把成功与金钱和名利联系在一起\n但实际上 它是一种心态
Most people associate success with money\nand power, but really it's a state of mind.
你说这话时需要骑在摩托车上?
You had to be on a\nmotorcycle to say that?
提到成功时 它唯一的局限就是\n它是无极限的
And when it comes to success the only\nlimit is that there are no limits.
我不知道你居然知道如何站在马的旁边\n太了不起了
Hey, I didn't know you knew how to\nstand near a horse; that's impressive.
Barney 我不太明白 你在这些片段里什么都没做啊
Barney, I don't get it. You don't do\na damn thing in any of these clips.
很正确 因为这就是企业美国人所需要的
Exactly. Because that's who\ncorporate American wants--
看起来像勇敢的冒险者 但事实上什么都不做
people who seem like bold risk\ntakers, but never actually do anything.
事实上做事才会让你失业
Actually doing things gets you fired.
实际上 我正在写有关这个现象的书
In fact, I'm wting a book\non this very phenomenon.
你真的正在写书?
Really, you're writing a book?
不是 那会是... \n你到底听我说没?
No, that would be doing\nsome... Are you even listening?
我一生 都怕错过可能的事情
All my life, I have dared\nto go past what is possible.
为了做到不可能的?
To the impossible?
正是 到达那个可能
Actually, past that-- to\nthe place where the possible
与不可能相会而成的...
and the impossible meet to become...
可能的不可能
the possimpible.
可能的不可能? 你说真的吗?
The possimpible? Really?
用你自己的语言展现你的创造性和远见...
Inventing your own word\nshows creativity and vision...
创造性远见
Vizha-tivity.
如果让我给你一个建议的话 \n它是:
If I can leave you with\none thought, it's this:
没有任何事 一切事\n都是有可能的不可能
Nothing-- and everything--\nis possimpible.
Barney Stinson Barney Stinson\nBarney Stinson, Barney Stinson
一个了不起的人
That guy's awesome
你是不是又...
Is that you agai...
是你在唱这首关于你自己的歌?
Are you singing a song about yourself?
当然不是 那样也太烂了
Absolutely not. That would be lame.
Stinson Barney Stinson\nsinging this song\nStinson, Barney Stinson\nsinging this song
那就会真的很烂
That would be really lame
认为这个家伙很了不起的崇拜者之一
One of the many admirers\nwho think that guy's awesome
完美!
Perfect and available
Awesome awesome awesome,\nawesome awesome awesome...\nAwesome, awesome, awesome,\nawesome, awesome, awesome...
Awesome awesome Awesome awesome,\nawesome awesome awesome awesome...\nAwesome, awesome Awesome, awesome,\nawesome, awesome, awesome, awesome...
被雇用了
HIRED
这给我带来了十一份儿工作
That baby got me 11 job offers.
不 不可能
No. No way.
Barney 你那个很荒谬可笑
Barney, that was ridiculous and insane.
神经又荒谬
Insane-ulous.
- 给我做一个\n- 什么?
- Make me one.\n- What?
- 恩 你终于说出来了\n- 什么?
- Yes, now you're talking.\n- What?
我都快被驱逐出境了\n任何方法我都会试
I'm about to be deported.\nI'll try anything.
好吧 我们该开始了
Okay, we better get started.
还有很多要拍摄 \n而且我那儿你的那些镜头不能用
There's a lot to shoot, and I don't think I can\nuse any of the footage I already have of you.
你那儿有我的什么镜头?
What footage do you already have of me?
我们该开始了
Let's just get started.
哦 亲爱的
Oh, sweetie.
你还在为舞者髋关节的玩笑郁闷吗?
Are yostill upset about\nthe dancer's hip jokes?
没有
No.
我们只是开玩笑而已 \n我们都知道那是因为打篮球受的伤
We were just kidding. We all\nknow it's a basketball injury.
恩 当然是
Yeah, totally.
Lily 有些事我得告诉你
Lily, I have something\nI need to tell you.
什么事?
What is it?
我跳过很多舞
I dance more than you know.
什么?
What?
我跳的舞...
I dance...
比你想象的多
more than you know.
我不知道该怎么回答了
I don't know how to respond to that.
那么 Robin \n成为记者对你意味着什么?
So, Robin, what does being\na reporter mean to you?
- 恩 当我还是一个孩子的时候 我总是...\n- 停!
- Well, ever since I was a little kid, I always...\n- Cut!
Robin 你在说具体的细节
Robin, you're getting\nbogged down in specifics.
我要你说些含糊的听起来自信的流行词
I need you to just say vague,\nconfident-sounding buzzwords,
就像"协作作用"和"物力论"
like "synergy" and "dynamism."
你可以自己造个词 \n像... "联系活动"
You can make up a word,\nlike... "linkativity."
让我听起来像白痴一样怎么会让我被雇用?
How will sounding like an\nidiot get me hired anywhere?
好吧 那不要那么做
Okay, fine. Don't do it.
不管怎样 \n我相信你可以回顾很多发生在加拿大的趣事
Anyway, I'm sure there are plenty of\nexciting stories to cover back in Canada.
我刚读了\n温尼伯市长的侄子在冰下捉了条16磅的鼓眼鱼
I just read that the mayor of Winnipeg's nephew went\nice fishing and caught himself a 16-pound walleye.
来自世界上最糟地方的现场报道 \n我是Robin Scherbatsky
Reporting live from the worst place\nin the world, I'm Robin Scherbatsky.
好 可以 \n开始吧
Okay, fine. Roll camera.
相连的态度
Connectitude.
很好
Love it.
变质
Transformatation.
就这样
Earn it!
关联活动
Linkativity.
恩 关联活动是我的词
Yeah, linkativity's mine.
那么 你跳了多少舞?
So, how much dancing\nare we talking about?
我不知道... 我想应该说... 差不多多吧
I don't... I guess I'd say... medium.
你怎么跳那么多舞 为什么我不知道?
Why are you dancing so much,\nand why don't I know about it?
我一个人的时候才会那么做
It's-It's something\nI do when I'm alone.
你知道 就像如果有什么好事发生 \n我就会很兴奋需要活动下 然后就...
You know, like if something good happens, I\nget excited and I need to move, and I just...
我不知道 我不想谈这个了
I don't know. I don't want to\neven talk about this anymore.
那么你是因为跳舞才受伤的?
So that's how you injured your hip?
嘿 你听见没? \n今天只上半天班 我们两点就可以走了
Hey, did you hear? They're giving us\na half day today. We can leave at 2:00.
太好了! 谢谢 Herm
Great! Thanks, Herm.
Barney 这些服装太奇怪了
Barney, these costumes are ridiculous.
而且 这套亚马逊女战士公主服\n让我得了皮疹
Plus, the Amazon Warrior\nPrincess armor gave me a rash.
卡片在桌上 你不是第一个穿这衣服的
Cards on the table-- you weren't\nthe first lady to wear that in here.
但是它能给你力量 \n接下来是这个 现在你要做的是...
But it conveyed power. And so will\nthis. What I need you to do now...
用前额把这15块砖打破
is break these 15 bricks\nwith your forehead.
什么? 但是你在你的视频里面什么也没做
What? But you didn't do a\ndamn thing in your video.
你只是站在马的旁边 坐在摩托车上
You just stood near a horse\nand sat on a motorcycle.
那是因为我是男人 而你是女人
That's because I'm a\nman. You're a woman.
人们认定你什么都做不了
The assumption is that\nyou can't do anything.
但是你要向社会证明假设是错的
But you have to prove society wrong.
我没办法用前额打破15块砖
I can't break 15\nbricks with my forehead.
Robin 现在不是1950年了 \n你可以的
Robin, it's not 1950\nanymore. Yes, you can.
我要走了
I'm out of here.
什么? 为什么?
What? Why?
这根本不能帮我找到工作
None of this is going\nto help me get a job.
我就要被赶出这个国家了
I'm about to get kicked\nout of the country.
我知道我该做什么
I know what I have to do.
Lottery Girl是在这儿面试吗?
Is this where the Lottery\nGirl auditions are?
对 是这儿
Yeah, right here.
那 你姑姑Robin到达了人生最低潮
So, your Aunt Robin had\nreached her low point.
她去Lottery Girl面试了
She was auditioning\nto be the Lottery Girl.
- 今晚的号码是...\n- 停
- And tonight's Lotto numbers are...\n- Hold it.
按按钮之前说台词
Say the line before\nyou press the button.
- 这样能设置悬念\n- 这样能设置悬念
- It builds the suspense.\n- It builds the suspense.
好的
Okay.
今晚的号码是...
And tonight's Lotto numbers are...
- 17...
- 让她停下
- seventeen...\n- Stop her.
停
Hold it.
她为什么那样说?
Why did she say it like that?
就好象看到17号她不开心
It's like she's not even\nhappy about the 17 coming up.
她看起来很小气
She seems mean.
是 她看起来非常小气
Yeah, she seems super-mean.
你可以再说一边"17"吗?
Can you take another run at "17" for us?
\nSeventeen.
好吧 我都不明白她在干什么
Okay, I don't even\nunderstand what she's doing.
让我再试试
Let me try something.
试着幽默一点
Try being a little more wry.
幽默? 关于17?
Wry? About the number 17?
- 幽默 再加一点...\n- 闪耀
- Wry, with a little bit of a...\n- Twinkle.
闪耀
twinkle.
\nSeventeen.
很好!
That was great!
嘿 Marsh 我给你拿了点淡啤
Hey, Marsh, I got you a light beer.
我知道你们舞者都很注意卡路里的
I know how you dancers are\nalways counting calories.
一点都不好笑 好不好?
It's not funny, all right?
医生说如果病情加重 我就得做手术
The doctor says if it gets any\nworse, I might need surgery.
阴道重建手术?
Vaginal rejuvenation surgery?
你知道大学期谁没有在阴道手术?
You know who didn't do a lot of\noperating on vaginas in college?
- 谁?\n- X博士
- Who?\n- Dr. X.
他做的很好!
He did just fine!
你们知道吗? \n你们应该把这些不好的从你们简历上去掉
You know what? Both of you geniuses need\nto take that weak-ass crap off your r\sum\s.
我是说 你已不是X医生 你也不再灌篮了
I mean, you are not Dr. X anymore,\nand you cannot dunk anymore.
让这些都过去吧
Let it go.
那Marshall和我是在坐唯一简历有缺点的?
So Marshall and I are the only people at this\ntable with "weak-ass crap" on their r\sum\s?
你在暗示什么?
What are you implying?
我不知道!
I don't know!
1995年7月4号还有印象吗?
Does the date July 4,\n1995 mean anything to you?
你个贱人
You son of a bitch.
时间到! 新的冠军是 \n29个热狗 Lily "大肚"Aldrin
Time! And the new champion, with 29\nhot dogs, Lily "The Belly" Aldrin.
这跟教育孩子有什么关系?
How is that relevant to\nteaching kindergarten?
这可以教孩子们...
It teaches kids that...
我可以很快吃完很多热狗
I can eat a lot of\nhot dogs very quickly.
是 但你再也吃不了了!
Yeah, but you can't do it anymore!
你再也不能投篮 女士的大腿!
You can't dunk anymore, Ladyhips!
你竟敢这么说! 这腿可以...
How dare you! These hips can...
伙计们, 伙计们!
Guys, guys!
我没有通过Lotto Girl面试
I didn't even get the Lotto Girl gig.
我得回加拿大了
I have to move back to Canada.
我不敢相信
I can't believe this.
我还记得搬到这儿的前一晚
I remember the night\nbefore I moved down here.
他们为我开了送别派队
They threw a going-away party for me.
他们给了我一个照相机\n这样我就可以把我的照片寄给他们
They gave me a camera so I could\ntake pictures and send them home.
大家都很肯定我会成功
And everyone was so sure I was\ngonna be such a big success.
我会想念你们大家的
I'm really gonna miss you guys.
怎么了?
What happened?
Robin要回加拿大了
Robin has to move back to Canada.
哦 天啊 太糟了
Oh, my God. How awful.
我是说 你回去又回来路好长啊
I mean, for one thing it's\ngonna be a really long commute.
你什么意思?
What do you mean?
我完成了你的视频简历
I finished your video r\sum\ on my own.
寄给了这儿所有电视台
Messengered it to every\nstation in the city.
八频道的一个人打来了电话
A guy from Channel Eight called.
他喜欢你
He loved you.
他想让你去试镜
He wanted you to come in and audition.
哦 天啊!
Oh, my God!
我告诉他不行 \nRobin Scherbatsky不会去试镜
I told him no. Robin\nScherbatsky doesn't audition.
他要么就给你这份工作否则免谈
He gives you the job or nothing.
我得到那份工作了?
So I got the job?
没 他骂了我然后把电话挂了
No. He cursed me out and hung up.
但是12频道又来了电话 他们也想要你
But then Channel 12\ncalled. They also loved you.
他们让你主持新的早间谈话节目
They offered you a job hosting\ntheir new morning talk show.
Barney 太棒了!
Barney, that's amazing!
- 我告诉他们不行\n- 伙计!
- I told them to shove it.\n- Dude!
这样会让他们更想要你
Which only made them want you more.
所以 他们又多给了百分之十的薪水
So, they jacked up their\noffer by ten percent.
恭喜你 Scherbatsky小姐
Congratulations, Miss Scherbatsky.
看来你要留下了
It looks like you're gonna have to stay.
你不会想要跳舞的 是吧?
You're not about to dance, are you?
哦 不 我很好 我\n会晚一点再跳
Oh, no, I'm good. I'll do it later.
你是怎么做到的?
How did you pull this off?
我是可能的不可能的主人
I am the master of the possimpible.
你的确是 谢谢你
You really are. Thank you.
所以 由于Barney叔叔 \n我们得让Robin姑姑留下了
So, thanks to your Uncle Barney,\nwe got to keep your Aunt Robin.
而我们其他人\n决定让一些事情成为历史
And the rest of us decided it\nwas time to let some things go.
恩 除了Lily
Well, except for Lily.
时间到!
And... time!
多少?
What's the count?
33个!
Thirty-three!
\n******
午餐食谱=种族歧视
MEAL PLAN=RACISM
为什么没人来我的抗议呢?
Why is no one coming to my Happenings?